https://www.rcbawards.com/shopping-cart/site/store-policies.php

RCB Awards | Crystal Awards - Outdoor Plaques - Cast Bronze Plaques
Stone Awards
Trophies | Build Yours Now!
Copyright
Logos, photos and other artwork provided by clients are assumed to comply with all applicable copyright laws.
Marketing
By placing an order with us, you grant us the right to use sample images of your finished goods for our marketing purposes. To opt out of this, let us know before approving the proof of your order.
Deposit and Payment on Orders
All orders must be paid in full prior to us filling the order. If you have elected check payment option on your order, we will begin processing your order after we receive the full payment for the order. Alternative payment methods available for immediate processing of your order include Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover Card Payments. An order is not accepted unless you receive an order acknowledgement from us through e-mail or fax.
Return/Refund
All Orders are provided on a Custom Basis. Each award is designed, assembled and personalized with engraving and/or silk screening, and once built it is non-returnable as it cannot be sold to other customers due to the custom nature of the item in question.
If there is an error in engraving or other personalization method utilized, that is due to an error on our part, you may request a return merchandise authorization to return the item within 15 days after the date your order was shipped or delivered and we will make any corrections at our expense with like or similar item as may be available.
There is No Refund even if the engraving is due to an error on our part. We will correct any errors, or re-engrave with the correction on a new item of similarity. Any spelling errors on the customers part are the responsibility of the customer. - We can only engrave what we are asked to engrave and as a general policy we do not proof, or spell check text submitted by a customer as there are valid reasons to mis-spell certain words.
All orders will be submitted to the customer as a proof via a PDF or other image format through e-mail. Customer must sign off on the proof before any engraving or personalization will be performed. Please ensure you return the proofs to our company as quickly as possible as to not delay the shipping of your awards.
If a return is authorized you will be issued a return merchandise authorization (RMA) The RMA number must appear on the outside of the package being shipped back. Shipments received without an RMA will not be accepted by our shipping department and will be returned unopened to the sender.
Any returns accepted by our company that do not follow the above procedure are subject to a 25% restocking fee. Any shipping charges assessed are non-refundable. The restocking fee and shipping charges will be deducted from the credit issued back to credit cards and/or any checks that are cut as a result of the return, before the credit is issued. The amount of the credit will be less the restocking fee and applicable shipping charges.
Returned Checks/Disputed Credit Card TransactionsThere is a $35.00 returned check service charge, and/or allowable collection and payment fees as allowed by civil code. We do not accept a personal check or credit card payments to replace a check that has been returned. If a check is returned, the face value of the check, plus the 35.00 returned check fee may be paid by cashiers check.
There is a $35.00 late payment fee for disputed credit card transactions that will be assessed for all disputed card transactions wherby a customer has not contacted us prior to contacting your bank. If there is an error on a transactions, you should always contact the merchant first as we can resolve the issue quickly, and without the hassle of a dispute. In addition, finance charges at the rate of 1.5% per month will be assessed on all disputed credit card transaction until payment is received in full.
Pricing ChangesWe reserve the right to modify the pricing provided with or without notice. We make every effort to ensure our pricing listed in our online catalog is accurate and a pricing change would only occur in the case where an error is discovered on a product. You will be notified of the pricing change and have the opportunity to cancel your order should this occur.
By ordering your awards from our company, you agree to these terms and conditions. If you have any questions concernings these policies, please feel free to contact us
Privacy Policy
Please note that this Use Policy is subject to change without notice, and that it reflects our current business practices. This Use Policy is dated March 1, 2010
PERSONAL INFORMATION AND CHOICE"Personal information" is information about a natural person that identifies or describes an individual, including, but not limited to, his or her name, social security number, physical description, home address, home telephone number, education, financial matters, etc, readily identifiable to that specific individual. A domain name or Internet Protocol address is not considered personal information, however, it is considered "electronically collected personal information."
According to Government Code 11015.5., "electronically collected personal information" means any information that is maintained by an agency that identifies or describes an individual user, including, but not limited to, his or her name, social security number, physical description, home address, home telephone number, education, financial matters, medical or employment history, password, electronic mail address, and information that reveals any network location or identity, but excludes any information manually submitted by a user, whether electronically or in written form, and information on or relating to individuals who are users, serving in a business capacity, including, but not limited to, business owners, officers, or principals of that business.
"Electronically collected personal information" that we automatically collect includes your domain name or Internet Protocol address, and statistical information about which web pages you visit on our web site. If you voluntarily participate in an activity that asks for specific information (i.e., completing a request for assistance, adding products to a shopping cart, submitting an order, sending an e-mail, or participating in a survey) more detailed data will be collected. If you choose not to participate in these activities, your choice will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature of this web site.
If any type of personal information is requested on the web site or volunteered by the user, State and Fedral law, including the Information Practices Act of 1977, Government Code Section 11015.5., and the federal Privacy Act of 1974 may protect it. However, this information may be a public record once you provide it, and may be subject to public inspection and copying if not otherwise protected by federal or State law.All Information submitted or collected by use of this web site is considered to be publicly accessible information.
A SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDRENChildren are not eligible to use services that require submission of personal information, and we require that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. This includes submitting personal information to us as part of a user profile or personalization profile, an order for products or e-mails. If you are a minor, you can use these services only if used together with your parents or guardians. If you are a minor, you should seek guidance from your parents.
INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW IT IS USEDWe do collect personal information directly from individuals who volunteer to use some of our services. Collection of this information is required to deliver the specific services such as fulfillment and completion of your order, but use of these services is voluntary.
If you do nothing during your visit to the web site but browse or download information, we automatically collect and store the following information about your visit:
The Internet Protocol Address and domain name used, but not the e-mail address;
The type of browser and operating system you used;
The date and time you visited this site;
The web pages or services you accessed at this site;
The web site you visited prior to coming to this web site.
The information we automatically collect or store is used to improve the content of our web services and to help us understand how people are using our services. This information does not identify you personally and is used for gathering web site statistics. The information we automatically collect and store in our logs about your visit helps us to analyze our web site to continually improve the value of the materials available. Our web site logs do not identify a visitor by personal information, and we make no attempt to link other web sites with the individuals that browse this web site.
This site may provide or distribute certain lists and statistical reports of regulatory information as provided by law, but no personal information is sold or distributed, and all relevant legal protections still apply to this web site.
WHAT HAPPENS TO INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT TO US?If you choose to submit information to us, the information may or may not be transmitted through secure lines to our company database. You will be notified whether the information submited is secure or not by your browser. Different browsers notify you using different methods. Please consult the documentation for the browser you are using for details on how your particular browser notifies you of security information. Any private information will only be used for the purposes for which it was provided and will not be shared with another entity except as prescribed by law and/or as necessary to fulfill your order request.
USE OF INTERNET REQUEST FOR ASSISTANCE FORM INFORMATIONAny information you provide to us will only be shared with entities involved in your order as necessary. Information you provide may be included with other consumers' information to be used for statistical reporting, trending data, and/or investigative actions. For example, we may need to retain information that becomes part of an enforcement action or consumer complaint case for a period of time after the closing date of your order. Typically orders are stored in our online database for a period of seven years for accounting purposes.
SURVEYSIf during your visit to this web site you participate in a survey or send an e-mail, the following additional information will be collected:
The e-mail address and contents of the e-mail; and
Information volunteered in response to the survey.
The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats you send us. The information is retained in accordance with Government Code 11015.5.
IF YOU SEND US E-MAILYou may choose to provide us with personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. Sometimes we forward your e-mail to other employees or third party organizations we work with who may be better able to help you, and this staff may be employed by a different agency or company. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations or, as required by law, we do not share your e-mail with any other organizations and your e-mail address is never solld to third party companies for use in spam activities.
We use your e-mail to respond appropriately. This may be to respond to you, to address issues you identify, to further improve our web site, or to forward the e-mail to another agency for appropriate action for the purpose of fulfilling your order request.
ORDER FORMSIf you place an order with us, we request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your order/request. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you.
PUBLIC DISCLOSUREAll information collected at this site becomes public record that may be subject to inspection and copying by the public, unless an exemption in law exists. In the event of a conflict between this Use Policy and the Public Records Act, the Information Practices Act, or other law governing the disclosure of records, the Public Records Act, the Information Practices Act, or other applicable law will control.
AUTOMATIC COLLECTION OF INFORMATION/COOKIESCookies are simple text files stored on your computer by your web browser. Some pages on this site may make use of cookies to provide you with personalized service on your return visits, or for other reasons as may be necessary to provide a good web site experience for you.
This site makes every attempt to avoid the use of cookies except when needed to maintain the functionality of an application.
Cookies created on your computer by using this web site may contain "personal information" but only if you submit that personal information to this site through our forms. You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer by using any of the widely available methods. However, if you turn your cookie option off, you may not be able to access some of the features in our interactive applications.
SECURITYThis Site, as developer and manager of this web site, has taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its telecommunications and computing infrastructure, including but not limited to authentication, monitoring, auditing, and encryption. Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation, and day-to-day practices of the entire sites operating environment as part of its continuing commitment to risk management. This information should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided via this web site. However, because of the Public Nature of the Internet, you should consider ANY AND ALL information submitted through, or listed at this site to be publicly and freely accessible. This site or it's owners make no representation or warranty to the contrary.
LINKS TO OTHER SITESOur web site has links to sites we feel might be useful to you and which may provide services. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
This web site and the information it contains are provided as a public service by the our company. This system is monitored to ensure proper operation, to verify the functioning of applicable security features, and for comparable purposes. Anyone using this system expressly consents to such monitoring. Unauthorized attempts to modify any information stored on this system, to defeat or circumvent security features, or to utilize this system for other than its intended purposes are prohibited and may result in criminal prosecution.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITYThis site attempts to maintain the highest accuracy of content on its web site. Any errors or omissions should be reported for correction.
We makes no claims, promises, or guarantees about the absolute accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this web site and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this web site. No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed, or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this web site or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.
Reference in this web site to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm, or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by this site or its employees or agents.
This Use Policy is subject to change without notice.
OWNERSHIPIn general, information presented on this web site, unless otherwise indicated, is copyrighted. and duplication of images, content or any other form of this site is prohibited by law. If you would like to purchase usage of images, or information from us you may contact us to make a request
PLEASE NOTE:
Please note that none of our products are designed to be used by children as toys or play objects. Our products are designed to be put in a special place for recognition and admiration, rather than for continuous handling.  As such, all of our products are intended primarily for use by people aged 13 years and older as recognition products. We do not reccomend that you let children 12 years or younger play with our products.
Information to Create Awards
FAQ
Shipping Time
Online Ordering Guide
Award Text Suggestions
Policies
About Us
Schedule an Appointment
RCB Awards | Crystal Awards - Outdoor Plaques - Cast Bronze Plaques 8000 W. Capitol Drive
Milwaukee, WI 53222Phone: (414) 479-9100
Powered by BizWizard ShopKart by NetSoft Studio, LLC.
© Copyright 2007-2020
All Rights Reserved.Privacy Policy
SHOWROOM HOURS: Monday through Friday 9 AM to 5 PM.
